hi and welcome to new every day my name
안녕하세요, 매일 새로운 이름으로 오신 것을 환영 합니다.
is Carrie my name is Jen and on today
Carrie입니다. 제 이름은 Jen이고 오늘입니다.
show we're picking up in week 3 of the
우리가 3 주째에
parable of the sower with rocks
바위와 씨 뿌리는 자의 비유
dangerous
위험한
welcome back to the show so whether
쇼에 오신 걸 환영 합니다.
you've tuned in again and we have we are
너는 다시 조정했고 우리는
going back to talk about the parable of
다시 비유에 대해 이야기하기 위해
the sower SM to finish up the last
마지막 씨를 끝내기 위해 씨 뿌리는 사람 SM
couple of examples that Jesus gave us
예수 께서 우리에게 주신 여러 가지 사례
about sowing a seed so I'll just tag in
씨를 파종하는 것에 관해서는 태그를 달아 놓을 것 입니다.
there done so we're going to pick up
거기서 우리가 데리러 갈거야.
we're going to read that passage from
우리는 그 구절을
the book of Matthew this is in the NIV
이 책은 마태 복음의 NIV에있다.
chapter 13 12 23 we're going to read the
13 장 12 23 우리는
whole thing because for some of you it
모든 일 때문에 당신 중 일부는 그것을
might have been a while since you've
네가 이래로 한동안 해왔 던 것 같아.
read this passage so here we go that
그래서 여기에이 구절을 읽어 우리는 간다
same day Jesus went out of the house and
같은 날 예수님이 집에서 나왔다.
SAT by the lake such large crowds
그런 군중에 의한 SAT
gathered around him that he got into a
그가 주변에 모여서
boat and sat in it while all the people
배를 타고 모든 사람들이 앉아 있는 동안
stood on the shore then he told them
그가 그에게 말했던 해안에 서 있었다.
many things in parables saying a farmer
많은 비유가 농부를 말하고있다.
went out to sow his seed as he was
그는 자기 씨앗 을 뿌리기 위해 나갔다.
scattering the seed some fell along the
씨를 뿌리다가
path and the birds came and ate it up
길과 새들이 와서 그것을 먹었다.
some fell on rocky places where it did
일부는 그것이했던 바위 같은 장소에 쓰러졌다.
not have much soil it sprang up quickly
토양이 많지 않아 빨리 번성했다.
because the soil is shallow but when the
토양이 얕기 때문에
Sun came up the plants were scorched and
썬이 식물을 태우고 마르고
they withered because they had no root
그들은 뿌리가 없어서 시들어 버렸다.
other seed fell among thorns which grew
다른 종자는 성장한 가시 가운데 떨어졌다.
up and choked the plants still other
그 식물을 아직도 질식시켜
seed fell on good soil were produced to
좋은 토양에 떨어진 종자는
crop a hundred sixty or thirty times
백 육십 또는 삼십 번 농작물
what was sown he who has ears let him
무엇을 뿌린 것입니까?
hear the disciples came to him and asked
제자들이 예수님 께 와서 물었다.
why they speak to people in parables he
비유 로 사람들과 이야기하는 이유
replied the knowledge of the secrets of
그 비밀에 대한 지식 을 답했다.
the kingdom of heaven have been given to
하늘의 왕국에 부여 된
you but not to them whoever has will be
너는 누구든지 그 사람과있을 사람이 아니야 .
given more and he will have an abundance
더 주어지면 그는 풍요 를 가질 것이다.
whoever does not have even what he has
그가 가지고있는 것조차 없는 사람
will be taken from him
그에게서 빼앗길 것이다.
this is why I speak to them in parables
이것이 내가 비유로 그들에게 말하는 이유입니다.
though seeing they do not see though
비록 그들이 보지 못함에도 불구하고
hearing they do not hear or understand
그들이 듣거나 이해 하지 못하는 것을 듣는다.
in them is fulfill the prophecy of
그들 안에서 예언 을 성취한다.
Isaiah you will be ever hearing but
이사야, 너는 들릴 것이다.
never understanding you will be ever
너를 결코 이해하지 못할 것이다.
seeing but never perceiving for this
보고 있지만 결코 이것을 인식하지 못함
people's hearts have become callous they
사람들의 마음이 냉담 해졌다.
hardly hear with their ears and they
귀가 거의 들리지 않는다.
have closed their eyes otherwise they
그렇지 않으면 눈을 감았 다.
might see with your ear eyes hear with
너의 귀 눈으로 들릴지도 모른다.
your ears and understand what their
당신의 귀와 그들이 무엇을 이해하는지
hearts and turn and I would heal them
마음과 방향 을 바꾸면 나는 그들을 치료할 것이다.
but blessed are your eyes because they
그러나 그들은 당신의 눈을 축복했습니다.
see in your ears because they here for I
귀에서 볼 여기에 그들이 I에 대한 때문에
tell you to choose many prophets and
많은 예언자를 선택 하라고 말씀 하십시오.
right to spend long to see what you see
당신이 보는 것을보기 위해 오래 머무를 권리
but did not see it and to hear what you
그러나 그것을 보지 않고 당신이 듣는 것
hear but do not hear it listen then to
들리지만 들리지는 않는다.
what the parable of the sword means when
언제 칼의 비유가 의미 하는가?
anyone hears the message about the
누구든지 그 메시지를 듣는다 .
kingdom and does not understand that the
왕국 을 이해하지 못한다 .
Evil One comes and snatches away what
사악한 사람이 와서 무엇을 치는지
was sown in his heart this is the seed
그의 마음 속에 뿌려졌다 이것은 씨앗이다.
so along the path the one who received
그래서 경로를 따라받은 사람
the seed that fell on rocky places is
바위 같은 장소에 떨어진 씨앗 은
the man who hears the word and at once
한 마디로 그 말 을 듣는 사람
receives it with joy but since he has no
기쁨으로 받아 들여지지 만
root he lasts only a short time when the
그는 짧은 시간 동안 만 지속된다.
trouble or persecution comes because of
곤란이나 박해는
the word he quickly falls away the one
그는 빨리 그 단어를 빠져 나간다.
who received the seed that fell among
그 중에서 씨를받은 사람
the thorns is the man who hears the word
가시는 그 말을 듣는 사람이다.
but the worries of this life and the
그러나이 삶의 걱정과
deceitfulness of wealth choke it making
부의기만은 그것을 질식시킨다.
it unfruitful
유익한
but the one who received the seed that
하지만 씨앗을받은 일이
fell on good soil is the man who hears
좋은 땅에 떨어 졌다는 것은 듣는 사람이다.
the word and understands it he produces
그 단어는 그가 생산하는 것을 이해한다.
a crop yielding a hundred sixty or
백 육십 또는
thirty times what was sown this is the
뿌려진 것의 30 배
word of the Lord so just we want to do a
주님의 말씀, 우리는 단지
quick review here this seed is and I
이 시드는 바로 여기에서 빨리 검토됩니다.
love love asking review questions so I'm
사랑에 대한 질문을하므로
going to ask questions care is going to
질문을 할 것입니다.
answer let's see how much she remembers
대답 그녀가 얼마나 기억하는지 보자.
ok what is the seed the word of god jack
좋아, 씨는 신 잭의 말
ok how does the sower so the sea
좋아 씨 뿌리는 사람은 바다가 어때?
generously abundantly nice 242 what or
넉넉한 풍부하게 좋은 242 무엇이나
how does the path become the path from
어떻게 경로가에서 경로가됩니까
people walking on it
사람들은 그것에 걸어
Thanks alright why does the evil one
감사합니다. 왜 악한 일을하는 겁니까?
steal the sea but it doesn't take root
바다를 훔치지 만 뿌리 내리지 않는다.
and producer
생산자
is that right yeah
그게 맞습니까?
cuz he knows it will cuz it's so good
사촌 그가 그렇게 잘할 거라는 걸 안다.
because he is so good yo its to see that
왜냐하면 그는 그렇게 좋은 것을 보았 기 때문이다.
Satan would not steal the seat if it was
사탄은 그것이 있었다면 자리를 훔치지 않을 것입니다.
not good that's true how is hard ground
좋지는 않다. 어떻게 단단한 땅 이냐.
softened well
부드럽게 잘
when we talked in previous shows if
이전 쇼 에서 이야기 할 때 if
someone's heart was hard it was softened
누군가의 마음이 굳어서 부드럽게되었다.
through the love of other
다른 사람의 사랑을 통해
nothing what wet flaws are frozen heart
젖은 결함이 얼어 붙은 것은 아무것도 없다.
an act of true love an act of true like
참된 행위는 참된 행위를 좋아한다.
he frozen Thank You frozen so we titled
그는 냉동 감사합니다.
this that one I didn't think this was
이 사람은 나는이 생각하지 않았다
going to be a Disney review but we could
Disney 리뷰가 될 수는 있지만
do disney review but we're not really
디즈니 리뷰를해라. 그러나 우리는 정말로 아니다.
sure how that would connect so we titled
그것이 어떻게 연결되어 우리가 제목을 붙 였는지
this saying rocks are dangerous so where
이 말하는 바위는 위험한 곳입니다.
I say rocks are dangerous they are
나는 바위는 그들이 위험하다라고
dangerous I think of falling rocks
위험한 바위를 생각해.
avalanches etc I pay me by dangerous
눈사태 등 나는 위험한 사람 에게 돈을 지불한다.
well I
나는
dangerous because if you throw a rock
위험이 바위 던져 때문에
and you can kill them that's true I you
너는 그들을 죽일 수있어. 나는 너야.
can trip on a rock we were we were
우리가했던 바위에 여행 할 수있다.
hiking and we're always whenever I go
하이킹을 할 때마다 항상 우리는 하이킹 중입니다.
hiking like ha if i was to trip and fall
내가 여행과 추락한다면 하처럼 하이킹
what would happen and normally as I
무슨 일이 벌어지고 정상적으로
hidden Rock that I you know that we
우리가 알고있는 숨겨진 바위
stumbled on or yeah that yeah and so
비틀 거 렸 거나 예, 그렇습니다.
it's like hot rocks can be very
그것은 뜨거운 바위처럼 아주있을 수 있습니다.
dangerous and like we think in the way
위험하고 우리가 생각 하는 것처럼
that they can those are very obvious
그들은 그것들이 매우 명백 할 수있다.
ways that rocks can harm us but when you
바위가 우리를 해칠 수 있지만 당신이
think about a plant if they are planted
심어 져 있다면 식물에 대해 생각해보십시오.
in rocky soil the root system actually
바위 토양에서 실제로 뿌리 체계
stays along the top of the soil because
토양의 꼭대기를 따라 머물러 있기 때문에
the rocks are there like they they can't
바위는 그들이 할 수없는 것처럼 거기에있다.
get past it they can't get pass it and
지나치게되면 통과 할 수 없으며
so they can't actually go down in times
그래서 그들은 실제로 시간 안에 갈 수 없다.
of drought and I can't reach the water
가뭄과 나는 물에 도달 할 수 없다.
if there's under water system yes and so
그렇다면 물 시스템 아래에 있다면
rocks actually impede
바위는 실제로 방해한다.
how deep someone's our a tree's roots go
누군가가 우리 나무의 뿌리가 얼마나 깊은 지
down they also so they absorb the water
그들도 물을 흡수하도록
they also are not the rocks but the
그들은 또한 바위가 아니라
roots and so this is how important the
뿌리와 이것이 얼마나 중요한지를
roots are and it was interesting because
뿌리가 있고 재미 있었기 때문에
I thought it was studying this I guess
나는 그것이 내가 추측하고있는 것을 연구하고있다라고 생각했다.
they never really thought about how
그들은 정말로 어떻게 생각했는지 결코 모르겠다.
important routes are the plans and yet
중요한 경로는 계획이며 아직
roots gives stability if you some trees
너에게 나무가 있으면 뿌리가 안정성을 주네.
have more underground root system then
지하 루트 시스템이 더 많다.
they have above system and that's real
그들은 위의 시스템을 가지고 있고 그것은 진짜입니다.
purpose of getting water and gaining
물을 얻고 얻는 목적
nutrients and also they are storage
영양소 와 또한 그들이 저장됩니다
system in times of drought and so if
가뭄의시기에 체계가 있다면
it's you know dry out then the the roots
그것은 당신이 알고 건조한 다음 뿌리
actually store the waters are they are
실제로 물을 저장하고있다.
the result the reserve so they you know
그 결과 당신이 아는 예비군
and they regulate what's going on there
그리고 그들은 그곳에서 벌어지는 일을 규제합니다.
their nutrient regulators in the rest of
나머지 영양소 규제 자
the tree which I thought very
내가 생각했던 그 나무
interesting how how important routes are
중요한 경로가 얼마나 흥미로운 지
and yet it says that some fell on rocky
그래도 일부는 바위에 떨어 졌다고 말합니다.
places where it did not have much soil
토양이별로없는 곳
it sprang up quickly because the soil
그것은 토양 때문에 신속하게 일어났습니다.
was shallow but when the Sun came up the
얕은 것이었지만 태양이 올 때
roots were scorched and they withered
뿌리가 마르고 쇠약 해졌다.
and I'm like the rocks got in the way of
그리고 나는 바위가 길에 들어온 것 같아.
the plant producing fruit okay so if we
과일을 생산하는 식물은 괜찮습니다.
were good because obviously this isn't a
분명히 이것이 a가 아니기 때문에 좋았다 .
lesson in agriculture in fact I needed
사실 농업에 대한 교훈이 필요했습니다.
to ask some of my anger culture friends
내 분노 문화 친구들에게 물어봐.
tell me about roots why are what's
뿌리에 대해서 말해봐
important and it was great because they
중요하고 그들은 훌륭했기 때문에
told me but the question is like what
나에게 말했다. 그러나 질문은 무엇과 같다.
does that actually mean for us like why
그 이유는 우리에게 실제로 의미가 있습니까?
would why would Jesus say that you know
왜 예수님은 당신이 알고 있다고 말씀 하시겠습니까?
it sprang up quickly because the soil
그것은 토양 때문에 신속하게 일어났습니다.
was shallow so what does it mean that
얕은 것이 었습니다. 그래서 그것은 무엇을 의미 합니까?
like he goes on to explain it that the
그는 계속해서 그것을 설명하기 위해
one who received the seed that fell on
떨어진 씨앗을받은 사람
rocky places is the man who hears the
바위 같은 곳은 사람들이 듣는 곳입니다.
word and at once receives it with joy
한마디로 기쁨으로 받아 들인다.
well that would be my first question is
그게 내 첫 질문이 될거야.
why did he receive it with joy well we
왜 그는 기쁨으로 그것을 받았습니까?
can I talked about this and it's like
수 나는 이것에 대해 이야기하며 같다
well
잘
if you're if the soil of your heart is
당신의 마음의 토양이
shallow yeah what what does that
얕은 그래 무슨 일이 있는지 무엇을
actually mean because it's it's
그것이 실제로이기 때문에 실제로 의미합니다.
affecting how he actually perceives the
그가 실제로 어떻게 지각하는지에 영향을줍니다.
sea right yeah and so well I think he
바다 바로 네와 너무 잘 나는 그가 생각
receives it with joy because it's good
그것이 기쁘기 때문에 기쁨으로받습니다.
like it's called the good news like what
무슨 좋은 소식이라 불리는 것 같아요.
do you mean I get to go to heaven like
당신은 내가 좋아하는 천국에 갈 얻을 의미합니까
what do you mean I can have peace like
내가 평화 를 가질 수 있다는게 무슨 뜻이야?
what do you mean I can have joy what do
너 내가 무슨 기쁨을 가질 수 있단 뜻이야?
you mean I can be set free like it's
너는 내가 자유롭게 할 수 있다는 뜻이야.
like yeah yeah I want all those things
좋아, 나는 그 모든 것들을 원해.
and people want Jenny Wiley want all of
사람들은 제니 윌리가 모든 걸 원해.
those things they want to receive those
그들이 받고 싶은 것들
things with with joy because it is
그것이 기쁨과 함께 있기 때문에
joyful but I had listened to someone
즐겁지 만 나는 누군가의 말 을 들었다.
discuss this who said they received it
그들이 그것을 받았다고 누가 이야기하는지 토론 한다.
with joy but that was actually a sign
기쁨으로 그러나 그것은 실제로 표시이었다
that maybe they didn't fully understand
어쩌면 그들은 완전히 이해하지 못했을 것입니다.
the gospel of the Cross was about and
십자가 의 복음은
that they needed to repent so it's the
회개 해야 할 필요가 있음 을
full understanding yeah what it means to
완전한 이해 그래, 그것이 의미하는 것
follow Christ because it's one thing to
그것이 한 가지이기 때문에 그리스도를 따른다.
receive a gift but it's something else
선물을 받지만 다른 것
totally to actually walk it out
완전히 실제로 그것을 밖으로 걷는
because I can receive a gift for
내가 선물을받을 수 있기 때문에.
Christmas and be like yeah this is nice
크리스마스와 네가 멋지다는 것이 좋다.
nice coat nice coat and then it hangs in
좋은 외투 좋은 외투 및 그 후에 걸린다
my closet and people can say well why
내 옷장과 사람들은 왜 그런지 말할 수 있습니다.
are you not wearing that coat and i'm
그 코트를 안 입니?
like i'd have to put it on
나는 그것을 입어야 만 할거야.
like I'd have to I received it with joy
내가 기쁨으로 그것을 받아야하는 것처럼
that's it like wow this is an amazing
와우처럼이게 놀랍습니다.
coat look how warm it is in it and then
코트 가 얼마나 따뜻해 보이는지 살펴 봅니다.
it's like oh man it's it's going to be
오, 그게 그렇게 될거야.
so bulky when I sit in the card I'm
카드에 앉아있을 때 부피가 커서
gonna have to get it cleaned if it gets
도착하면 청소해야합니다.
dirty and you can come up with all sorts
더러운 당신은 모든 종류를 생각해 낼 수 있습니다.
of reasons why you don't actually put
왜 실제로 넣지 않는지에 대한 이유들
the coat on even though it protects you
코트는 당신을 보호 하더라도
from winter right it keeps you warm and
겨울부터 그것은 따뜻하게 지켜줍니다.
so when we talk about receiving the
그래서 우리가
gospel with joy it's like receiving that
기쁨으로 복음을 전한다.
coat it's like ah yeah and then it's
코트 그것은 아, 그래 그리고 그것의처럼
like well what do you mean in order to
당신이 하기 위해서 무엇을 의미합니까?
receive and utilize it I'm going to have
그것을 받고 그것을 활용한다. 나는 가질 것이다.
to repent so we're going to pause for a
회개하기 위해 우리는 잠시 멈추고
commercial break we want you to think
상업적인 휴식 우리는 당신 이 생각하기를 원한다.
about that for a second have you wear
초 동안 그건 당신이 착용이에 대해
your life have you received the gospel
너의 삶은 네가 복음을 받아 들였어.
and you want it but yet you're not
너는 그것을 원 하지만 너는 그렇지 않다.
really willing
정말 기꺼이
to walk it out
그것을 밖으로 걷다
let's move back after this Jeff Weston
이 제프 웨스턴 후로 돌아 가자.
Yemen you're building a brand-new
예멘 당신은 새로운 건물을 짓고 있습니다.
beautiful website what are you all right
아름다운 웹 사이트 무엇이 당신 괜찮아요
you're terrible actor what does we're
너는 끔찍한 배우 야 우리가 뭘하는거야?
acting comes into play I don't know
연기는 나도 몰라.
where I think you're supposed to act
네가 행동해야 한다고 생각하는 곳.
okay I'm building a really cool website
좋아요 . 정말 멋진 웹 사이트를 만들고 있어요.
are you building a really cool website
정말 멋진 웹 사이트 를 만들고 있습니까?
you need hosting one of the things about
당신은 그 중 하나에 대한 것들을 호스팅해야합니다.
a hosting account is you don't want to
호스팅 계정을 사용하고 싶지 않습니다.
have limitations put on your website
웹 사이트에 제한이있다.
let's sure how much hard drive space do
얼마나 많은 하드 드라이브 공간을 확보할까요?
you have how many email accounts how
얼마나 많은 이메일 계정이 있는지
many domains can point to it well we've
많은 도메인이이를 잘 나타낼 수 있습니다.
got an amazing deal for you for a very
아주 놀랐지.
limited time cat five dot TV / dreamhost
제한 시간 고양이 5 도트 TV / dreamhost
for just five dollars and a bit of
단지 5 달러와 약간 을 위해
change per month you are going to get
당신이 얻으려고하는 매월 변화
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
무제한 호스팅 웹 사이트 무제한
email accounts on that hosting service
해당 호스팅 서비스의 이메일 계정
you are also going to receive a free
당신은 또한 무료로받을 것입니다
domain name the rules are your own com
도메인 이름 규칙은 귀하 자신의 com입니다
dice to put that amazing website that
그 놀라운 웹 사이트를 넣을 주사위
you've been working on on there if you
너는 거기서 일하고있어.
run if you want to build a wordpress
당신이 wordpress 를 만들고 싶다면 달린다.
site fine sign up cat five dot TV /
사이트 괜찮 가입 고양이 5 도트 TV /
dreamhost just don't put the peddle the
꿈의 호스트 그냥 행상 넣어 하지 마십시오
papers are just don't do it but hey it's
서류는 그냥하지는 마세요.
a great deal folks best deal you're
훌륭한 거래를하는 사람들이 당신을 가장 잘 다룰 것입니다.
gonna find five dollars and change per
5 달러를 찾아서 한 번에 바꿀거야.
month go to cap five dot TV / dreamhost
달 모자 / TV / dreamhost에 5 달 간다.
welcome back to new every day we're
우리가 매일 새로운 것을 다시 환영합니다.
containing continuing our show of a
우리의 쇼를 계속 포함
parable of the sower
씨 뿌리는 자의 비유
being a parable of the rocky soil so
바위 같은 토양의 비유이기 때문에
Jenny left us with a question the
제니 는 우리에게 질문을 남겼습니다.
question is I wanted you to think about
질문 은 당신이 생각하기를 바란다는 것입니다.
just how have have you received the
너는 어떻게 너를 받았 는가?
gospel but you're struggling with areas
복음하지만 지역과 싸우고있어.
of actually walking it out that whole
전체 를 실제로 걷는 것
idea of giving it up like giving up
포기하는 것과 같은 포기의 생각
things and the thing is it's that
사물과 그 것이 그것입니다.
letting go of sin well because if the
죄를 버리는 것이
roots can't get down like what are those
뿌리는 그것들처럼 엎어 질 수 없다.
rocks yes and so rocks our sin is the
예 바위 등 우리의 죄가이다 바위
sin in our life you might be thinking
우리의 삶 에서 죄 가 생각할지도 모른다.
about I was forgiven of the sin well yes
나는 죄의 용서 받았다. 그렇다.
when we come to Christ we are forgiven
우리가 그리스도 께 나아가면 용서 받는다.
of our sins when we choose to repent but
우리가 회개하기로 선택할 때 우리의 죄를
it's the sinful nature it's those things
그것은 죄의 본성입니다.
that kick I like I always say yes the
그 차는 내가 항상 그렇다고 말하는 것을 좋아한다.
old has gone the new has come a second
낡은 것은 새로운 것을 갔다.
Corinthians 5 17 the old has gone the
고린도 전서 5 장 17 절은
new has come but the old nature will
새로운 것이 왔지만 오래된 자연 은
still kick which is why some people say
아직도 어떤 사람들이 말하는 이유는 킥.
well I thought I have been set free from
잘 나는 내가 자유 로워 졌다고 생각했다.
this and the answer is yes you have been
이것과 대답 은 예스입니다.
set free from the power of it in your
당신의 힘에서 자유를 얻으십시오.
life but you still have a willful choice
너는 여전히 고의적 인 선택을하고있다.
to to follow in that way so it's that
그렇게해서 그렇게해라.
sinful nature that's Romans 772 25 and
Romans 772 25 의 죄 많은 성격
but then it's also mindset it's that way
하지만 그런 식으로 생각 하는 것입니다.
of thinking okay
괜찮아.
give you an example like like way of
너에게 너 같은 식으로
thinking that becomes an impediment to
생각이 장애물이된다.
growth yes so supporting me and like an
성장 예 그렇기 때문에 나를지지하고
example would be what we've always done
예를 들어 우리가 항상 해왔 던 것입니다.
it this way like like my parents never
이런 식으로 부모님처럼 절대로
said it was wrong to go into a store and
가게에 가서 잘못했다 및
not put something in your pocket and
주머니에 무언가를 넣지 및
walk out with it right so you've always
그것으로 오른쪽으로 나가서 항상 그렇게했습니다.
done that like it just and so at you
너처럼 그걸 좋아해.
know to walk in and go oh no this is
들어가서 가야할지 아냐.
wrong right you actually have to change
틀린 권리 당신은 실제로 변화해야한다.
the way that you think to be like I was
네가 그렇게 생각 하는 방식이야.
never told this was wrong but now I
이것이 잘못되었다는 말은하지 않았지만 지금은
realize it is wrong well you know what I
잘못을 실감 잘 알고 내가
can think of an example is a family
예를 가족 이라고 생각할 수있다.
member of mine when he became a
내 회원이 될 때
Christian never thought anything about
그리스도인은
like the magazines that are at the
상기되는 잡지 등
checkout and now
결제 및 지금
you know it's often women like if
당신은 그것이 종종 여성과 같이
there's even topless women on the front
정면에 토플리스 여성조차있어.
of magazines and he never thought
잡지는 생각도 못했고
anything about it yeah just nice to look
그것에 관한 무엇이라도 보는 것은 단지 멋지다.
at but then after he came to Christ he
그러다가 그는 그리스도 께 나아 갔다.
found that it really bothered him which
그것이 정말로 그를 귀찮게한다는 것을 알았 습니다.
was very interesting because that was a
그것이 매우 재미 있었기 때문에
change of heart then what I like he had
마음이 바뀌다가 내가 좋아하는 것이있다.
me wise to see it right and so is that
나 지혜는 바로 그래서이다 볼 수
those mind says in Romans 12 2 says be
그 마음은 로마서 12 장 2 절에
transformed by the renewing of your mind
당신의 마음을 새롭게함으로써 변화된
that whole idea we have to ask Christ to
우리가 그리스도 께 구해야 할 그 모든 생각
renew our mind and if righteousness is
우리의 마음을 새롭게하고 , 의가 있으면
being set apart for God right living
하나님의 옳은 삶을 위해 분열되어있다.
that when God looks at us he sees the
하나님이 우리를 바라 볼 때 그는
righteousness of his son mm-hmm and I
아들의 의로움 mm-hmm and I
think about if the seed is the word of
씨앗이
God and Timothy it says that the Word of
하나님 과 디모데는 말씀의
God is useful for teaching correcting
하나님 은 올바른 가르침에 유용합니다.
rebuking and training in righteousness
꾸짖음과 의로 훈련
doing what is right I think that God
옳은 일을하는 것은 하나님이라고 생각합니다.
actually loves and that produces good
실제로 사랑하고 좋은 결과를 낳는다.
things in your life and good things and
당신의 삶과 좋은 것들과
those around you mm-hmm and so to put to
너 주위에있는 사람들.
grab ahold of that word of God and use
그 말씀을 붙잡고 사용하라.
it for those things let it letting it
그 것들을 위해 그것을 시키도록해라.
speak into your life to remove those
너의 삶에 말로 그 사람을 제거하라.
sinful the mindsets or when you read it
죄책감이나 생각을 읽었을 때
and you challenge though maybe it's
어쩌면 당신은 도전 할 수 있습니다.
unforgiveness or pride or selfishness
용서 또는 자부심 또는 이기심
right those are all sins that can be so
바로 그것들은 그렇게 될 수있는 모든 죄입니다.
hard to let go of and you know you can
당신이 할 수있는 것을 알기가 어렵습니다.
think well I thought why can't I just do
난 그냥 이유를 할 수 없다 생각 잘 생각
this well sometimes it isn't you're so
이 아니라 때때로 당신이 너무 것 아니다
used to doing things you've trained your
네가 훈련 한 일을하는 데 익숙해 져.
mind to do to be selfish and you don't
이기적으로하기 위해해야 ​​할 마음이 있고 그렇지 않다.
even realize that you're being selfish
심지어 당신이 이기적인하고 실현
until you read the Word of God that sort
당신이 하나님의 말씀을 읽을 때까지
of just oh I am being selfish i am being
그냥 오, 나는 이기적이다. 나는있다.
unkind i am being prideful about
나는 자만심이 강하다.
something and so those are if we don't
우리가하지 않으면 무언가 가 있습니다.
remove those rocks right which are
그 바위들을 제거하라.
illuminated by the Holy Spirit through
성령의 지시로
the power of reading the word then they
그 다음 단어를 읽는 힘
create impediments to the roots going
가는 뿌리에 장애물을 만든다.
down
내려가는
you know I was just thinking about the
내가 너를 생각하고 있었어 .
passage I think it's in James
통과 제임스에 있다고 생각합니다.
where
어디에
he talks about how kindness leads
친절에 이르는 방법 에 대해 이야기 합니다.
holiness leads to brotherly kindness
성결은 형제애에 인도한다.
leads to love there's a hole right
거기에 구멍이있어 사랑에 ​​빠지다.
walking through of different attributes
서로 다른 속성들
that should be possessed increasing
그 소유가 증가해야한다.
measure in the Christian life right
그리스도인의 삶에서의 올바른 측정
right and it says if you're not growing
맞아, 자라지 않는다면
in these areas I am paraphrasing then
이 분야에서 나는 그 말을 바꿔 쓰고있다.
it's because you've forgotten that
그걸 잊어 버렸기 때문이야.
you've been forgiven of your past sin
너는 과거의 죄를 용서 받았다.
so sometimes Jen I wonder
그래서 때로는 Jen I wonder
mine's that's because people don't
내 것이 사람들이하지 않기 때문입니다.
actually
사실은
grasp the idea that i am forgiven and i
용서 받았다는 생각을 붙잡아 라.
don't have to do those things
그 일을 할 필요가 없다.
and I struggle with that sometimes
그리고 나는 때때로 그와 투쟁한다.
because I don't we've talked about this
왜냐하면 우리는 이것 에 관해서 이야기하지 않았기 때문입니다.
a lot how when a sin is identified
죄가 밝혀지면 어떻게 많이
I am not so prone to introspection to
나는 반성에 열중하지 않는다.
identify where it comes from and all
그것이 어디서 왔는지, 어디서 왔는지를 알아 내라.
these things and get rid of it instead
이 일들 을 대신 제거하십시오.
of saying what God's dealt with it
하나님이 그것을 어떻게 처리 하셨는지 말하는 것
dealt with it and I just choose to
그것으로 처리 하고 나는 다만 선택 한다
believe it that I'm forgiven and move
용서 받았다고 믿는다.
forward from that and I realize maybe
앞으로 그걸로 나는 깨달을 것이다.
there's some aspects of life that that's
삶의 일부 측면이 있습니다.
not so easy to do but do you have
그렇게 쉬운 일은 아니지만 당신은 가지고 있습니까?
thoughts on that
그것에 대한 생각
with regards because I you know and
관련하여 나는 때문에 당신이 알고
Carrie and I have talked about the slugs
캐리와 나는 굼벵이에 대해서 이야기했다 .
I tend to be more introspective and
나는 좀 더 내성적 인 경향이 있고
saying or what is the root cause of this
말 또는이 근본 원인은 무엇입니까?
because I don't want to go back there
내가 다시 거기에 가고 싶지 않기 때문에.
anymore and giving over that i want to
더 이상주고 싶다 .
say the root cause area to God so that I
하나님 께 근본 원인을 말하면서
don't have to go back and so you do need
다시 갈 필요가 없습니다 그래서 당신이 필요합니까
the both end to say I have been forgiven
용서 받았다고 말하는 양쪽 끝.
of this I don't need to do this yeah and
이걸 할 필요 가 없어.
for me I I feel like you have to go back
나를 위해 II는 당신이 돌아 가야하는 것처럼 느낀다.
to well where did that first start and
처음에는 어디에서 시작 했습니까?
to heal up that place so that I don't
그 자리를 치유해서 내가하지 못하게해라.
have to continue to say but I've been
계속 말을해야하지만 나는
forgiven of that you know and I'm gonna
당신이 알고있는 것과 용서를 용서 했어요.
cough so hold on a second but I believe
기침은 잠깐 만요.하지만 저는 믿습니다.
it is the both and to recognize that we
그것은 둘다이며 우리가
have been forgiven but also just go to
용서 받았다.
that place and say God I don't I don't
그 장소와 말은하지 않는다.
want to go back to this area I don't
이 지역 으로 돌아가고 싶다.
want to do this anymore so why is it
그것을 이유 때문에 더 이상이 작업을 수행 할 수
that I continue to do this and you know
나는 이것을 계속 하고 너는 알고있다.
this passage talks about when the Sun
이 구절은 태양이 언제
comes out they the plant withers away so
그들이 나간다.
they receive it
그들은 그것을 받습니다 .
they spring up and then the Sun comes
그들은 솟아 나서 태양이 온다.
out and the plant starts to wither well
밖으로 나가고 식물은 잘 시들기 시작한다.
that's because they didn't have any
왜냐하면 그들은 아무 것도 갖지 않았기 때문입니다.
roots or they didn't count the cost of
뿌리이거나 그들은 비용을 계산하지 않았다.
following Christ and that that word us
그리스도를 따르고 그 말을 우리에게
up to fall away in the Greek is scandal
그리스에서 추락하는 스캔들
scandal is 0 or which action is like
스캔들이 0이거나 어떤 동작이 좋아
they were scandalized right there's like
그들은 거기처럼 스캔들이났다.
what do you mean I have to do this right
이 일을 올바르게해야 한다는게 무슨 뜻이야?
so they've they're okay they're like and
그래서 그들은 그들이 같이있어 괜찮아했습니다 및
we talk about this like the gospel is
우리 는 복음에 대해 이렇게 이야기합니다.
good news right Jesus came to die on the
좋은 소식은 바로 예수님은에 죽을왔다
cross for our sins so we could be set
우리의 죄를 위해 십자가에 못 박혀 우리를 놓을 수있다.
free from the power of sin so we can
우리가 할 수있는 죄의 힘으로부터 해방 될 수있다.
have relationship and God yay gospel
복음을 전하는 하나님 과 관계를 가져라.
woohoo like yes yeah and then there's
예, 그렇습니다.
scandalized by that what do you mean
그게 무슨 뜻 이야?
this is gonna take a little bit of work
이건 약간의 작업이 필요할 것입니다.
like what do you mean I have to give up
무슨 뜻 이죠처럼 내가 포기해야
everything what do you mean I have to
내가하는 모든게 무슨 뜻이야?
die to myself what do you mean I have to
당신은 내가해야 할 말은 무엇을 자신에게 죽어
give up my sin cuz the gospel is good
내 죄를 포기하라. 복음이 좋다.
news we can be made right with God but
우리는 하나님과 올바른 관계를 맺을 수 있지만
that means Jesus I deny yourself pick up
그건 내가 너 자신을 데려 간다는 것을 의미하는 예수를 의미한다.
your cross and follow me like
너의 십자가와 나를 따라라.
and you're like wait is like that's
그리고 당신은 기다리는 것과 같습니다.
people are hard like you're scandalized
너 스캔들 처럼 사람들은 힘들어.
that whole idea and even carry sad like
그 모든 생각 은 슬픈 것처럼 보입니다.
that idea of I have been forgiven like
나는 그 같은 생각 을 용서 받았다.
realizing that like you even have to
너처럼
claim the forgiveness it's not like I
용서를 요구한다.
want to say a free pass it's like you
너와 같은 자유로운 통과를 말하고 싶다.
have yes you have acid you love that
예, 당신이 좋아하는 산이 있어요.
concept of the gospel well the flip side
복음의 개념 플립 사이드
is now that you have to repent and you
이제 너는 회개해야하고 너는
have to allow the Holy Spirit to bring
성령 께서 가져 오도록 허락 해 주셔야 합니다.
up those rocks in your life those things
너의 인생 에서 그 바위들을 올려라.
those mindsets that pride that
자존심이있는 마음가짐
unforgiveness that selfishness so and
이기심을 용서하지 말라.
are actually offering them to him saying
실제로 그 (것)들에게 그 (것)들을 제안하고있다
would you please remove these from my
이걸 제발 제발 제발
life so that the roots of the good news
좋은 소식의 뿌리가되는 삶
and repentance can go deep so I can
회개가 깊어 져서 내가 할 수있다.
fully appropriate forgiveness the things
완전 하게 용서하는 것들
that I've been set free from in the
나는의에서 무료로 설정 한 것을
depths of my life and so it says I
내 삶의 깊이가 너무 깊어서
believe that the deeper you are with
너와 함께하는 것이 더 깊다고 믿어.
Jesus the last offended you will become
마지막으로 예수님께서는 당신을 불쾌하게하십니다.
because that gospel message has gone
그 복음의 메시지가 사라 졌기 때문에
sewing d is life-giving right it has
바느질 d는 생명을주는 권리 다.
tapped into i want to say with that
나는 그걸로 말하고 싶다.
passage in Psalms where it says lessons
시편에있는 구절은 그것이 교훈을 말한다.
is the man who does not walk in the
걸어 다니지 않는 사람입니다.
counsel of the wicked or stand in the
사악한 자의 권고 또는
way of center or sits centers are sit
센터의 방식 또는 센터가 앉는다.
within the seat of mockers but de la his
라 조롱의 좌석 만 드 내 자신의
delight is in the law of the Lord and on
기쁨은 주님 의 율법 에 있습니다.
his law he meditates day and night he is
그의 법은 그가 밤낮으로 명상하고있다.
like a tree planted by streams of water
물줄기에 심어진 나무처럼
which yields its fruit and seas
그 과일과 바다 를 산출하는
and whose leaf does not wither whatever
그 잎이 무엇이든 시들지 않는다.
he does prospers you know Jen when I
그는 내가 너를 알고 번영한다.
heard that first I thought the tree
처음에 나는 그 나무가
isn't planted in the river it was beside
옆에있는 강에 심어 져 있지 않다.
it which means that the roots have to go
그것은 뿌리 가야 한다는 것을 의미 한다.
down and reach the waters yes so in
물에 빠지다.
order for those roots to go down and
위해서는 그 뿌리가 아래로 이동하는 방법과
reach the water source the rocks have to
바위가 가져야 할 수원에 도달한다.
come up like the rocks have to be dealt
바위처럼 다루어 져야한다.
with so the question is I love asking
그래서 질문은 내가 묻는 것을 좋아한다.
questions I just ask questions all the
질문 나는 단지 모든 질문을한다.
time that's how you get so smart care is
시간이 이렇게 똑똑해지면
also going to ask the questions FYI the
또한 FYI에 질문 할 것입니다 .
question is what are the rocks in your
질문은 당신의 바위 가 무엇인가하는 것입니다.
life like what are the rocks that are
바위가있는 것 같은 삶
impede the roots from coming down so
뿌리가 내려 오는 것을 방해한다.
that when the like because you can sort
그 때 당신이 정렬 할 수 있기 때문에
of sense it in your life is like when
너의 인생에서 감각의 때 처럼
that Sun comes out right and it says the
태양이 오른쪽으로 나오고
Sun it shines on the reins on the
태양은 고삐에 빛난다.
the weekend the the righteous and the
주말하여 의인과
wicked right so the Sun comes out on
사악한 권리로 태양이 나옵니다.
everyone and it's like where where do
모두와 어디서하는 것처럼
you feel like your withering Dean yes
네 쇠약 해지는 딘처럼 느껴져.
and then come though ask the question
질문 을하러 와서
Lord why is it that I feel so weak in my
주님 , 제가 왜 그렇게 약해 보 입니까 ?
faith when this happens because is there
거기에 있기 때문에 이것이 일어 났을 때의 신앙
an opinion and impediment there is there
거기에 의견과 장애가있다.
a rock there that's that my roots aren't
거기 바위가 내 뿌리가 아니라는거야.
going down deep enough my faith isn't
내 믿음이 충분히 깊어지지 않을만큼 깊은 곳으로 내려가.
strong enough and yes it's true you can
충분히 강해서 그렇습니다.
have the faith of a mustard seed you can
네가 할 수있는 겨자씨의 신념을 가져라.
move mountains but what is it that when
산을 움직여 라.
that thing happens you start yes I'm
그 일이 네가 시작하는 거야.
melting like oh please don't ask me to
그런 식으로 녹아 내게 부탁 하지마.
do that or the fear comes in or whatever
그렇게하거나 두려움이 들어 오거나 뭐든간에
well is that because the roots are
그 뿌리가
hitting against something and actually
뭔가에 맞서 실제로
like you said haven't don't have the
네가 말했듯이
freedom to get down into that water of
그 물에 빠져들 수있는 자유
life giving strength
생명력을주는 생명
so why you think about that
왜 그렇게 생각하니?
and I'm going to do some good thinking
나는 좋은 생각을 할거야.
on that so thanks for leaving us with
그걸로 우리 를 떠나 줘서 고마워.
that Jack do you want to pray for us
잭, 우리 를 위해기도하고 싶니 ?
sure Heavenly Father thank you so much
하나님 아버지 께 감사드립니다.
for your word and how it reveals and
당신의 말과 그것이 드러내는 방법과
Lord would you show us in our life the
주님 , 우리 삶에 우리를 보여 주시겠습니까 ?
rocks that are impeding us from our
우리를 방해하는 바위
roots going deep down and drinking up
뿌리 깊은 아래 로 마시고
your life giving water and Lord if
물과 주님을주는 당신의 삶 if
there's unrepentant in our hearts would
우리 마음 속에 회개하지 않는 것이있다.
you show that to us we don't want
너는 우리에게 원하지 않는 것을 보여 준다.
anything separating us from you
너와 우리를 나눠 줘.
Lord we're in the areas of our life
주님, 우리는 삶의 영역에 있습니다.
where we love thats it
우리가 좋아하는 곳
would you convict our hearts and help us
너는 우리 마음을 믿어 우리를 도울 까?
to surrender to you we ask this in your
당신에게 항복하기 위해
name
이름
thanks for tuning in again and we hope
다시 조정 해 주셔서 감사 드리며 희망합니다.
that you will ponder some of those
너는 그것들 중 몇 가지를 숙고 할 것이다.
questions and grow in a deeper
질문하고 더 깊이 자라다.
relationship with the gods or so much
신들과의 관계
they'll have a great week
그들은 멋진 한 주를 보낼거야.
you
당신